// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Most famous sweet of Karnataka?",
    answer: "Mysore pak",
    options: [
      "obbattu",
      "jamoon",
      "Mysore pak",
      "kai metai"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "First kannada dynasty of Karnataka?",
    answer: "Kadamba",
    options: [
      "Kadamba",
      "Chola",
      "Chalukya",
      "Mughal"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Classic dish of Karnataka?",
    answer: "Bisi bele bath",
    options: [
      "Mosaranna",
      "Puliogare",
      "Vangi bath",
      "Bisi bele bath"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Unique dance drama form of Karnataka?",
    answer: "Yakshagana",
    options: [
      "Katakali",
      "Kuchupudi",
      "Yakshagana",
      "Bharatanatya"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "When was Mysore state established?",
    answer: "1st,November 1956",
    options: [
      "11th, Febuary 1960",
      "1st,November 1956",
      "3rd, december 1952",
      "1st, Janauary 1950"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Total number of Districts in Karnataka?",
    answer: "31",
    options: [
      "35",
      "40",
      "31",
      "37"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Tagline of Karnataka tourism",
    answer: "One state many worlds",
    options: [
      "Blisful Karnataka",
      "One state many worlds",
      "Incridible Karnataka",
      "Gods own country"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "State flower of Karnataka",
    answer: "Lotus",
    options: [
      "Sunflower",
      "Sampige",
      "Jasmine",
      "Lotus"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "State tree of Karnataka",
    answer: "Sandal wood",
    options: [
      "Teak",
      "Sandal wood",
      "Rose wood",
      "Rubber wood"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The first city in asia to light up the streets on electricity",
    answer: "Bengaluru",
    options: [
      "Kolar",
      "Bengaluru",
      "Mysore",
      "Tumkur"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "The state emblem of Karnataka?",
    answer: "Gandabarunda",
    options: [
      "Gandabarunda",
      "Garuda",
      "Rose ringed Parakeet",
      "Chakra"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "The state animal of Karnataka?",
    answer: "Elephants",
    options: [
      "Tiger",
      "Deer",
      "Elephants",
      "Lion"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Rebelious queen of Karnataka?",
    answer: "Kitturu Rani Channamma",
    options: [
      "Keladia Channamma",
      "Rani Abbakka",
      "Rani lakshimi bhai",
      "Kitturu Rani Channamma"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Worlds Biggest monolithic statue in Karnataka",
    answer: "Gommateshwara",
    options: [
      "Gommateshwara",
      "Gautham buddha",
      "Staue of Liberty",
      "Statue of unity"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Highest peak of Karnataka?",
    answer: "Mullayana giri",
    options: [
      "Nandhi hills",
      "Mullayana giri",
      "Brahmagiri hills",
      "Kemmangundi"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Karnataka is the largest _____ exxporter in the country",
    answer: "Coffee",
    options: [
      "Coffee",
      "Sandal wood",
      "Spices",
      "Sugar"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];